<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mrboran.github.io/ml-knowledge-primer/blog</id>
    <title>ML knowledge primer Blog</title>
    <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mrboran.github.io/ml-knowledge-primer/blog"/>
    <subtitle>ML knowledge primer Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://mrboran.github.io/ml-knowledge-primer/img/favicon.ico</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting Slow!]]></title>
        <id>https://mrboran.github.io/ml-knowledge-primer/blog/start-slow</id>
        <link href="https://mrboran.github.io/ml-knowledge-primer/blog/start-slow"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The purpose of this blog post is to capture the learning in my development process. This learning]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The purpose of this blog post is to capture the learning in my development process. This learning
can be technical and non-technical. In the spirit of building in public rather than stealth,
I believe it's essential to share both the successes and the challenges encountered along the way.</p>
<p>Embarking on a journey of personal development, whether in programming, design, or any other field,
is often accompanied by a plethora of lessons. Some come from the joy of discovering new solutions,
while others stem from the frustration of debugging stubborn issues. Regardless, each experience
contributes to growth and understanding.</p>
<p>In this blog, I aim to document not just the end results of my projects, but also the journey that
leads to them. From wrestling with intricate lines of code to navigating the complexities of project
management, every step offers an opportunity for reflection and improvement.</p>
<p>Moreover, I recognize that learning extends beyond technical skills. Soft skills such as
communication, time management, and resilience are equally vital in the pursuit of personal and
professional excellence. Thus, I intend to explore these aspects as well, sharing insights gained
from both triumphs and setbacks.</p>
<p>By openly sharing my experiences, I hope to foster a community of learners who can relate to the
challenges and triumphs encountered in the development process.</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Madhur</name>
            <uri>https://mrboran.github.io/</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="first" term="first"/>
    </entry>
</feed>